ebrandon.ca 2018-11-23

# eBrandon.ca - Brandon, Manitoba's Online Community

Privacy Policy

**Policy Overview**

eBrandon.ca is privately owned and operated by Sobkow Technologies Inc of Brandon, Manitoba. We are very concerned about the protection of online privacy for all our website visitors. This policy is intended to provide an overview of our philosophy and procedures concerning this issue. This policy applies to the website www.ebrandon.ca. 

**Information we collect**

As part of the features of this website we do collect personally identifiable information voluntarily submitted by a visitor in connection with registration or other activity. With the permission of a visitor who is 18 years of age or over, such personally identifiable information submitted in connection with a registration or other activity on our website may be used for marketing and promotional purposes. Sobkow Technologies may also grant to certain third parties access to our database as necessary in connection with services provided by such third parties to the eBrandon.ca, but such disclosures are subject to non-disclosure commitments by the third parties. Information gathered online is used by Sobkow Technologies, for internal marketing analysis and to improve our products, services and websites. 

We use "cookie" technology (where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor's computer) to track user participation. We do not automatically extract personally identifiable information in this process. The "cookie" technology will only be used to track non-personal information such as type of browser, operating system, and domain names to customize the website for each visitor and to improve the visitor's online experience. In some instances, when contact information has been provided by the visitor, we will send notices to visitors, usually in the form of an e-mail. These notices, sent periodically, will announce website upgrades, new product information, promotions and other similar admins that may be of interest to the visitor. Our mailers and other notices tell the visitor how to "opt-out" so that he or she can stop the notices at any time. Cookie technology is also used to remember information specific to yourself in association with classified ad submissions ONLY when you indicate that you would like the site to remember your contact information for future use. This information is used for no other purpose other than your own computer remembering your information for future use by yourself.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We have integrated the Twitter widget of the company Twitter Inc. in the News section of this website. When you visit the news section you automatically load the Widget for display, and Twitter receives certain information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, and the address of the website where the Widget is integrated, and places a cookie that recognizes your browser. In connection with the cookie, Twitter can theoretically recognize which pages you have visited across various websites, provided that the Widget has been implemented there. On Twitter’s own account, Twitter uses the data to tailor content for you based on your visits to third-party websites, and may give suggestions for people to follow on Twitter, if you have a Twitter account. 

This website makes use of plug-ins operated by Facebook Inc, based in Palo Alto, USA. At various integration points throughout eBrandon, said plug-ins make use of a connection to Facebook’s servers to provide a conduit to eBrandon’s presence on Facebook. By default, if visiting eBrandon while logged into Facebook information related to your visit will be transferred to Facebook and in connection with your account will be used to present you with relevant content on an eBrandon page (for example a list of friends that have also ‘Liked’ eBrandon). You must log out of your Facebook account if you do not wish for this content to be shown or for this connection to be made. Should you choose to 'Like' eBrandon by clicking on the available button, that Like will be noted via your Facebook account. For more information on Facebook’s Data Policy, visit <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>. 

If at any time you wish to have your eBrandon member account removed from our database, please login to that account, click on the "Profile Settings" link in the left-hand column of your profile page and initiate remove from the link titled "Click for account removal form" under the subsequent settings tab. Should you have any difficulty with this process do not hesitate to send a request through the contact us page. 

We track and store user IP addresses each time a forum message, photo, video, classified ad, classified ad web form submission or private message are posted/sent. Combined with information from your internet provider, this information may personally identify you. This information will **only** be used in the event of a dispute between yourself and eBrandon or another third party in which the law is perceived to have been violated. 

Information (e-mail address) submitted as part of replies to classified ads is logged and is used only in the event of a legal dispute or in an emergency situation where those that have responded to an ad may need to be notified critical information relating to that ad. 

Your e-mail address is stored in our database for each classified ad you submit. This address is only used as a means for eBrandon to relay responses to your ad from your potential buyer to yourself. That address is never directly given to another user. It is internally used to link all ads you've posted on the "View all ads from this seller" page. 

Sobkow Technologies also collect personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and the like, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor as part of our various special feature and contest sections. In the case of online promotions and other activities, we do not condition a child's participation on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. 

You always have the right to request that contact information regarding you or your child be deleted from our database. To request deletion of your or your child's contact information in our database, please contact us using the information at the bottom of this page for more information. 

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by modifying this policy so all of our web customers are aware of our online privacy policy. Any questions or additional information can be obtained by contacting:

Sobkow Technologies Inc  
PO Box 20124 Brandon South PO  
Brandon, MB  
R7A 6Y8  
Phone: (204) 728 2407
